directorymaximizer.com 2014-02-09

# Maximizer E-Services Pvt. Ltd. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy   
Maximizer E-Services Pvt. Ltd.   

* * *

General Information   
Maximizer E-Services Pvt. Ltd. takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following information to learn more about our privacy practices. 

  * This policy covers what personally identifiable information Maximizer E-Services Pvt. Ltd. collects and how it is treated. Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify visitors to the http://www.directorymaximizer.com Web Site. This information may be limited to an IP address or extend to personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, or phone number. 
  * This policy only applies to http://www.directorymaximizer.com and does not extend to the practices of other Web Sites that we may link to, companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. 

* * *

Contact Information   
We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this privacy policy. 

Our Internet address is located at [http://www.directorymaximizer.com](http://www.directorymaximizer.com/)

**Maximizer E-Services Pvt. Ltd.  
2nd Floor, #60 Banaswadi Main Road   
Bangalore - 560033   
Karnataka, India**

You may contact us by e-mail at contact [ at ] directorymaximizer.com

* * *

Dispute Resolution   
Maximizer E-Services Pvt. Ltd. is committed to resolving any dispute you may have regarding our privacy policy quickly and efficiently. 

Disputes will be handled by our customer service representative. Our customer service will promptly correct any errors. 

* * *

Information Collection   
When visiting Web Sites certain information about you and your computer can sometimes be collected. This section explains what information Maximizer E-Services Pvt. Ltd. collects, and how it is used. 

Information Collected \- What information do we collect and why? 

We collect the following identifiable information about our visitors:

    * user.name    _(optional)_
    * user.home-info.online.email    _(optional)_
    * user.business-info.online.email    _(optional)_
    * dynamic.clickstream 
    * dynamic.searchtext 
    * dynamic.cookies 
  
We collect identifiable information for the following reasons: 
    * Completion and Support of Current Activity 
    * Web Site and System Administration 
    * Research and Development 
    * One-time Tailoring 
    * Pseudonymous Analysis 
    * Pseudonymous Decision 
    * Individual Analysis 
    * Individual Decision 
    * Contacting Visitors for Marketing of Services or Products 
    * Historical Preservation 
  
The details collected are only used for the purpose of rendering the services signed up for. E-mails will be sent to registered users only relating to the services the site renders and no promotional/advertorial e-mails shall be sent representing any third party. 

* * *

Information Recipients \- Who has access to the information collected?   

    * Ourselves and/or our entities acting as our agents or entities for which we are acting as an agent.   

* * *

Information Retention \- How long is this information retained?   

    * We do not have a retention policy for this area of the Web Site.  

* * *

Changing or Removal of Information   
You can review your personal information and make any necessary changes by logging in to your account and changing your preferences in the "My Account" area. You may email us at contact [at] directorymaximizer.com to remove your contact information from our database provided we have completed all pending transactions related to your account. 

* * *

Cookies   
Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web Site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. 

Our Web site uses the following cookies:

  * name="*" value="*" domain="*" path="*" 

As you browse our website, advertising cookies could also be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partners then enable us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with our website. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can opt out of such cookie tracking by contacting us. 

* * *
